educationalcoloringpages.com 2009-06-16

# Educational coloring pages privacy policy

**1\. Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure**

Your use of this site and/or your registration for products and services constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the site. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.  When this happens the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy will be amended.  In addition we will seek a customer’s prior consent, by email, for any new uses or proposed disclosures of information collected from the customer prior to the change. **  ** We will notify customers by email of changes to this policy that will affect information collected from them in the future.  In certain circumstances, however, we will not inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order. 

A customer may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time although this may result in suspension of the provision of products and or services to you.  If you unsubscribe within the guarantee period for any product and you request a refund the guarantee will be honored. 

**Mail (Electronic)**

During the course of your association with this website you may receive e-mails from us that contain information relating to you and the service(s) provided to you as a customer, including but not limited to Website changes, product additions, news and current updates concerning the industry, our Website and product availability. It is our policy to provide you with the opportunity to limit the use and/or disclosure of your personal information.If at any time you no longer wish to receive e-mail from us, just click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the page and request removal from our mailing list.

We collect the optin name and e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses and personal information of those who communicate with us via e-mail, or information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information or coloring competition etc. We don’t collect payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address by third party PayPal). 

This Privacy Policy has been implemented to protect personal information received from customers, and to respond to any inquiries.  The Privacy Policy also provides that will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties. 

**2 Purposes for Collecting Personal Information**

  * to understand customer needs regarding our services;
  * to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;
  * to fulfill your requests for products, services or information; 
  * to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from affiliates and third parties;
  * to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of this site; 
  * to develop and improve the products, benefits and services we offer to our customers and Website users 
  * to notify you of any hosted/run Competitions, new services or promotions from time to time 
  * to personalize some of our services and products for you and to deliver targeted advertisements and offers from and third parties;
  * to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request; 
  * to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the site or any product or service; 
  * to protect the services, products or rights this website, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the site;

**3.Limiting the Collection of Personal Information**

The collection of personal information is limited to that information which is necessary for Identified Purposes.  This site does not direct to the site, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of Law permitted.

When you visit the web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the site previously.  Cookies allow us to determine which products and services you have already purchased so that the site does not provide redundant information to you, and, if you are an affiliate, to track sales made to customers referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program.  If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the site.

A cookie is a small amount of information sent from a Web server to your computer. This site does not use cookies for marketing, promotional or advertising purposes, nor does it use cookies to track your Internet activity before or after you leave this Website.

**4.Disclosure, Processing and Retention**

This site does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:   
to ’s employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on ’s behalf for any of the following identified purposes:

As necessary if there is reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with ’s rights or property, other users of ’s web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and 

To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law. 

**5.Accuracy of Personal Information**

We will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information.  Customers are responsible for informing about changes to their personal information by sending an email to [support@educationalcoloringpages.com](mailto:support@educationalcoloringpages.com). (subject: update personal information) We will use new or updated personal information received from customers to update records. 

**6.Security Safeguards**

Reasonable steps will be take to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment accessed only by authorised persons. We will also take reasonable steps to protect personal information held from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification and disclosure.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorised access. We will continue to enhance these features as technology changes and becomes available.

Furthermore we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for any purpose. 

We will use reasonable efforts to protect customers’ personal information. 

**7.Access to Personal Information**

If is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer’s personal information, we will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney–client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.

Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting or the Privacy Officer as described above.  We will promptly correct such personal information. 

This information is your personal information and we will not disclose, leverage or sell this information to any other organisation under any circumstances, without prior permission, unless that information is absolutely necessary, for third parties that are involved in the processing of your order and are contracted to us to keep the information confidential or are required to comply with all relevant laws including the Privacy Act. Other ways we collect and use your personal information are to: 

If required by law or to enforce, protect or apply rights, we may release personal information as required. .

**8.Links to External Sites**

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online of which we have direct and total control of. We do not take any responsibility for our advertisers, outgoing links, or any other part of this site that is not under our direct or total control.. We advise that users read the Privacy Policies of external sites before submitting personal information.

Some of the hyperlinks on this Website may lead to other Websites that are not controlled by, or affiliated with us. In addition, other Websites may link to this Website. We have not reviewed these Websites and we are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these Websites.

If you have any inquirey reagding privacy please email us via contact us form.
